question_data =[
    {
      "type": "boolean",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "category": "General Knowledge",
      "question": "SCP-173 was the first SCP article written for the web-based collaborative fiction project known as the &quot;SCP Foundation&quot;",
      "correct_answer": "True",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "False"
      ]
    },
    {
      "type": "boolean",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "category": "General Knowledge",
      "question": "A pencil&#039;s lead is typically made from graphite, not lead",
      "correct_answer": "True",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "False"
      ]
    },
    {
      "type": "boolean",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "category": "General Knowledge",
      "question": "Popcorn was invented in 1871 by Frederick W. Rueckheim in the USA where he sold the snack on the streets of Chicago.",
      "correct_answer": "False",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "True"
      ]
    },
    {
      "type": "boolean",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "category": "General Knowledge",
      "question": "Furby was released in 1998.",
      "correct_answer": "True",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "False"
      ]
    },
    {
      "type": "boolean",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "category": "General Knowledge",
      "question": "Crystal Pepsi was first sold in US markets in 1993.",
      "correct_answer": "False",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "True"
      ]
    },
    {
      "type": "boolean",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "category": "General Knowledge",
      "question": "Cucumbers are usually more than 90% water.",
      "correct_answer": "True",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "False"
      ]
    },
    {
      "type": "boolean",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "category": "General Knowledge",
      "question": "Albert Einstein had trouble with mathematics when he was in school.",
      "correct_answer": "False",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "True"
      ]
    },
    {
      "type": "boolean",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "category": "General Knowledge",
      "question": "Coca-Cola&#039;s original colour was green.",
      "correct_answer": "False",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "True"
      ]
    },
    {
      "type": "boolean",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "category": "General Knowledge",
      "question": "The commercial UK channel ITV stands for &quot;International Television&quot;.",
      "correct_answer": "False",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "True"
      ]
    },
    {
      "type": "boolean",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "category": "General Knowledge",
      "question": "&quot;Typewriter&quot; is the longest word that can be typed using only the first row on a QWERTY keyboard.",
      "correct_answer": "False",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "True"
      ]
    }
  ]